[
  {
    "question": "Which president was the first to pardon a turkey?",
    "answer": "John F Kennedy",
    "choices": [
      "John F Kennedy",
      "Franklin Delano Roosevelt",
      "Joe Biden",
      "George Washington"

    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item of cutlery was only invented 10 years after the first Thanksgiving?",
    "answer": "The fork",
    "choices": [
      "The spoon",
      "The knife",
      "The fork",
      "The spork"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was pizza invented?",
    "answer": "Naples, Italy",
    "choices": [
      "Paris, France",
      "Naples, Italy",
      "New York, New York",
      "Boston, Massachusetts"

    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different shapes of pasta are there?",
    "answer": "Over 600",
    "choices": [
      "785",
      "Over 600",
      "Over 1200",
      "239"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What cheese is the Netherlands famous for making?",
    "answer": "Gouda",
    "choices": [
      "Cheddar",
      "American Cheese",
      "Swiss",
      "Gouda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What cheese is the Netherlands famous for making?",
    "answer": "Gouda",
    "choices": [
      "Cheddar",
      "American Cheese",
      "Swiss",
      "Gouda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a wiener schnitzel traditionally made of?",
    "answer": "Veal",
    "choices": [
      "Beef",
      "Lamb",
      "Veal",
      "Kangaroo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country consumes the most coffee?",
    "answer": "The Netherlands",
    "choices": [
      "The United States",
      "The Netherlands",
      "Brazil",
      "Portugal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was the popular curry, the chicken Tikka Masala invented?",
    "answer": "Glasgow, Scotland",
    "choices": [
      "Glasgow, Scotland",
      "Delhi, India",
      "Mumbai, India",
      "Chicken, Alaska"

    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What expensive shellfish were once seen as peasant food?",
    "answer": "Lobster",
    "choices": [
      "Lobster",
      "Oysters",
      "Limpets",
      "Clams"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fruit technically has a wasp inside of it?",
    "answer": "Figs",
    "choices": [
      "Papaya",
      "Figs",
      "Passion Fruit",
      "Mango"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Years Of Sushi Chef Training Does It Take To Be Trusted To Make The Rice?",
    "answer": "5 years",
    "choices": [
      "10 years",
      "1 years",
      "3 years",
      "5 years"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Peanut Butter Was Turned Into What Mineral By Scientists?",
    "answer": "Diamond",
    "choices": [
      "A Ruby",
      "Zinc",
      "Diamond",
      "Quartz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Nut Is Used To Make Dynamite?",
    "answer": "Peanuts",
    "choices": [
      "Almonds",
      "Walnuts",
      "Peanuts",
      "Cashews"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In What Country Was Ice Cream Invented?",
    "answer": "China",
    "choices": [
      "United States",
      "India",
      "Nigeria",
      "China"

    ]
  }
]
